<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leaderlessness Research Club</title>
    <link>http://leaderlessness.club/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Leaderlessness Research Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:20:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://leaderlessness.club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://leaderlessness.club/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:20:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://leaderlessness.club/about/</guid>
      <description>LRC: Leaderlessness Research Club Our mission is to practically implement and experiment with forms of leaderless organization, paving the path for other organizations to follow.
How we achieve our mission:
 Conduct and publish field research on existing organizations using leaderless organization Create and publish summaries, critiques, and reviews of existing materials on forms and anthropologies of (hopefully implementable) leaderless organization Facilitate discussions, offer presentations, and create general public events regarding implementing and experimenting with leaderless organization Offer feasible guides on implementation of great reductions of bureaucracy Offer guides on eschewing surveillance in regard to business ontologies, how do withdrawal forms of labor which managerialism cannot do without Publish original leaderless organization implementation manuals and guidebooks, report on experiments regarding our real world example-implementations of these manuals and guidebooks, from the high level overall system to the components (like consensus) Answer public questions on leaderless organization implementation  Interested in learning more?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>